

Soon-to-be graduate with degree of Bachelors of Technology in Computer Science & Engineering, specializing in Web Designing & C++. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects. Well-versed in numerous programming languages including HTML5, PHP, JavaScript, CSS, C++, MySQL. Also having background in basics of Cyber Security.

©

+91 7973108409

in Linkedin.com/in/ishaan-devsingla-a82449197



Ishaanpctebtech19cse.email@gmail.com

H. No. 2, Ghuman Estate, Sua Road, Threeke, Ludhiana, Punjab-142021

EDUCATION

PCTE Group of Institutes, Ludhiana, India
Bachelor of Technology in Computer Science &
Engineering
Expected graduation: 2023
Got 3rd university position in 3rd Semester
Got 2nd university position in 4th Semester

Lovely Professional University, Phagwara, India Diploma or Polytechnic in Computer Science & Engineering Got 8.59 CGPA

Guru Nanak Public School, Ludhiana, India Passed X class Got 7.6 CGPA

PROJECT EXPERIENCE

ONLINE SHOPPING WEBSITE NAMED AS PIKMARK 2022-present

- Prepared using HTML, CSS, JavaScript & PHP
- Online Shopping platform to buy goods
- It uses Razor-pay payment system
- It is presently in testing mode

KOSHISH WEBSITE

2021-present

- Made a website for college Festa week Koshish
- It is in live mode

FOOD WEBSITE

2020-present

- Made a working website on food and eatables
- It is also in live mode

PROGRAMMING & COMPUTER SKILLS

- Proficient in various programming languages including:
 - i. C++
 - ii. HTML5
 - iii. PHP
 - iv. JavaScript
 - v. CSS
 - vi. MySQL
- Have background in basics of Cyber Security, have completed various online certifications in the same
- Comfortable in making dynamic web project & websites
- Comfortable in poster making in Canva

KEY SKILLS

- Project management
- Strong decision maker
- Complex problem solving
- Coding
- Creative design
- Innovative
- Service-focused

CERTIFICATIONS

Programming Languages(certificate): **Programming in** C, C++, Core java, Oracle

10 CISA Certifications (ISACA'S Certified Information Systems Auditor)

Foundation Training in Web Page Development by CCIT – June 15, 2017

HOBBIES

- Playing Badminton and Football
- Playing Video Games
- Dancing
- Designing Websites
- Canva Poster Designing
- Martial Arts

LANGUAGES KNOWN English, Hindi & Punjabi